groono.com 2015-06-27

# Free Classifieds - Groono online classifieds

Groono handles your personal information with care. Groono respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the personal information that you share with us. You can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. Groono uses your information to provide our services with quality. We will help to resolve any disputes or problems. We promote safe trading and keep you up-to-date about our services. We are the owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to your information; Groono will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

Please take note that as a user, if you post personal information in any public areas of the Groono website, that information will be made public by you and available to viewers. Do not post information in public areas that you want to keep private. Information you post, share, or list with third parties like your buddies or any members of the social network about yourself may be shared with other users at your own risk.

Your information is safe: 

We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. No contact info should be listed or given out that you do not want seen while using Groono.com. Groono collects personal information when you register and when you use our products or services. 

Information submitted by Users on Groono:

• First name or first and last names   
• Gender  
• Age  
• Occupation  
• Location (city and state)   
• Photos  
• Videos or other shared content uploaded by the members 

Your Duty as a user: 

Groono may make changes to our privacy policy and the responsibility falls on the users to regularly review the privacy policy at all times.
